Carlos Bobadilla Jr

UX DESIGNER

Los Angeles, CA bobadilla.jr@gmail.com

SUMMARY

I'm a UX Designer. I deigned UI for 10+ years, but love developing.

My process goes from sketches, whiteboards to user flows, and I use Sketch. I'm a fan of HTML/CSS. I enjoy working in Illustrator and Photoshop. git is the greatest. I like reading

Designer News. I love the Lakers and catching the latest in mobile, at Pttrns.

OBJECTIVES

I'm currently a UX Designer at AppOne. I've previously worked with Handmade Mobile, 2Bit

Circus, and Netflix

In my free time I work on bHome App, a mobile blog community.

EDUCATION

Art Institute

Computer Animation/ Design

Santa Monica, CA

Graduated January 2001

EMPLOYMENT

AppOne

UX Designer

Santa Monica, CA

August 2014 - - Present

On a daily basis I am working on user flow for all company related IOS/Android, and working

on new designs for upcoming releases.

Handmade Mobile

Sr UX/UI Designer

Santa Monica, CA

January 2014 - - Present

- Develop Mobile Apps for native IOS
- UX user flows and structure
- Objective C, HTML5

Netflix

Sr. UI Art Director

Beverly Hills, CA April 2012 - - Present

- Maintained UI brand across multiple platforms
- Developed and presented conceptual solutions for web, iPhone, Xbox, and Playstation
- Assisted production managers in maintaining consistent user experience

Two Bit Circus

Sr. UX/UI Designer

Los Angeles, CA

December 2012 - - Present

- Directed and delegated to project creative team and outside vendors
- Created comps, storyboards, initial graphic concepts and final deliverables
- Built and maintained relationships with clients, partner agencies and other vendors.

Southpaw Digital

UX/UI Mobile Lead

Venice, CA

January 2011 - March 2012

- Produced iPhone, and roid, iPad games and advertising
- Presented and communicated concepts for clients and brand managers
- Conceptualized game visions and brand management across multiple platforms
- Interactive design for online and mobile advertising as well as e-commerce

Payoff.com

UI Designer/Illustrator

Culver City, California

July 2010 - January 2011

Payoff (http://payoff.com/) is a new platform that gives people the freedom to dream and live more purposefully. It's a free tool that uses a social gaming approach to help people take control of their money and reach their goals. Payoff inspires a deeper level of engagement in the game of real life.

Tapcode, Inc.

UX/UI Lead

Van Nuys, CA

September 2007 - October 2010

- Responsible for overseeing all design elements and maintaining company's visual image, including look and feel
- Directed and designed advertisement campaigns and promotions for outdoor spaces like the Hollywood and Highland center and Westfield Promenades
- Designed the UI and UX for self ordering systems for restaurants such as McDonalds,
 Burger King, and LAX
- Worked with the team of programmers to streamline interchanging assets and audio files to fit any brand
- Won Hospitality Magazine's Overall Technology Award in 2008 and UNLV's Excellence In Innovation Award in 2009

Stranger Adventures

Lead UI Designer

Santa Monica, CA

January 2005 - August 2007

- Designed interactive websites with a team of 6 flash designers
- As the lead UI designer, I worked to design a game type mechanic for a web based platform that gave users an addictive feel, resulting in a completely new way to interact online
- The interface designs were Nominated for 2 Emmy's. Outstanding Broadband Drama and Outstanding Achievement in Interactive Television for "Stranger Adventures"

uWink

UX/UI Designer/ Game Designer

Marina Del Rey, California

January 2000 - December 2005

- Designed tabletop touch-screen games
- Produced and delivered user flows to both internal & outsourced production teams

SKILLS

